<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MySpurs Player Profile</string>
    <string name="height_weight">Height / Weight</string>
    <string name="_180cm_68kg">180cm / 68kg</string>
    <string name="nationality">Nationality</string>
    <string name="indonesia">Indonesia</string>
    <string name="born">Born</string>
    <string name="_24_agustus_2000">24 Agustus 2000</string>
    <string name="rifqi_agustia">Rifqi Agustia</string>
    <string name="position">Position</string>
    <string name="right_back">Right Back</string>
    <string name="player_profile">Player Profile</string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Yves Bissouma</item>
        <item>James Maddison</item>
        <item>Pedro Porro </item>
        <item>Richarlison </item>
        <item>Cristian Romero</item>
        <item>Emerson Royal </item>
        <item>Davinson Sanchez </item>
        <item>Oliver Skipp </item>
        <item>Heung-Min Son </item>
        <item>Eric Dier </item>
        <item>Rodrigo Bentancur </item>
        <item>Fraser Forster </item>
        <item> Hugo Lloris</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_height_weight">
        <item>181cm, 72kg </item>
        <item>175cm, 72kg </item>
        <item>176cm, 68kg </item>
        <item>179cm, 71kg </item>
        <item>185cm, 82kg </item>
        <item>187cm, 75kg </item>
        <item>188cm, 77kg </item>
        <item>177cm, 66kg </item>
        <item>183cm, 76kg </item>
        <item>188cm, 87kg </item>
        <item>185cm, 73kg </item>
        <item>201cm, 92kg </item>
        <item>188cm, 78kg </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>On 14 June 2022, Tottenham Hotspur agreed a £30m deal for Bissouma.Three days later, Tottenham confirmed the signing of Bissouma, with the Malian signing a four-year deal. On 6 August, Bissouma made his debut for the club in the Premier League, coming on as a second-half substitute in a 4–1 win over Southampton. Born in the Ivory Coast and moving to Mali aged thirteen to pursue a professional football career, Bissouma participated at the 2016 African Nations Championship with Mali.In the semi-final against the Ivory Coast, he was brought on as a substitute in the 76th minute and scored the decisive goal to make it 1–0 in the 89th minute. However they went on to lose in the final against DR Congo.</item>
        <item>England international James Maddison joined us from Leicester City in the summer of 2023. James began his career with Coventry City where he progressed through the youth ranks to make his professional debut in August, 2014, before joining Norwich City in January, 2016. Remaining with the Sky Blues on loan for the rest of 2015/16 campaign, he finished with 42 appearances in total for his home town club, scoring five goals. An exciting creative midfielder, he made his debut for the Canaries in August, 2016, in an EFL Cup tie against his former side, before joining Scottish Premiership side Aberdeen on loan for the first half of the season, making 17 appearances and netting twice</item>
        <item>Pedro Porro joined us from Sporting CP in January, 2023, on loan until the end of the season, with an obligation to make the deal permanent in the summer. A versatile, flying machine down the right flank, Pedro played right wing-back, right-back and on the right of midfield in his 17 appearances, including 13 starts and three goals in the Premier League, where he was on target against Southampton, Manchester United and on the final day win at Leeds. Featuring twice against us in this season’s UEFA Champions League group stage, Pedro signed for Manchester City in August, 2019, but returned to Spain soon after to gain further first team experience, joining Real Valladolid on a season-long loan.</item>
        <item>Brazilian international Richarlison joined us from Everton in July, 2022, signing a contract until 2027. A forward who gives his all, the ball didnt fall for Richy in his debut campaign in a Spurs shirt. He scored three times for us in 35 appearances, including 18 starts, in all competitions in 2022/23. That included a night to remember, however, in September, as Richy marked his Champions League debut with both goals - both headers - in our opening group win against Olympique Marseille. He started up front for Brazil in the 2022 World Cup in Qatar and scored one of the goals of the tournament, a spectacular volley against Serbia that was later on the shortlist for the 2022 FIFA Puskas Award.</item>
        <item>Cristian Romero joined us from Atalanta in August, 2021 - and is now one of a select band of players who can call themselves World Cup winners. Defender Cuti became only the second Spurs player (ie, at the Club at the time) alongside Hugo Lloris - who he faced in the final - to lift the 2022 World Cup when Argentina beat Hugos France on penalties in a thrilling final in Qatar in December. Back in N17, Cuti had somewhat of a disrupted 2022/23, both through injury and the World Cup. He was injured just before departing for Qatar, missing five matches, and featured in 34 of our 50 matches, 33 starts, including 26 starts of 27 appearances in the Premier League. That took him to 64 appearances for us in all competitions.</item>
        <item>2022/23 proved another consistent season for the versatile defender, who featured on the right side of a central defensive three in the last four matches. He made 36 appearances in all competitions, including 26 in the Premier League, starting 27 times. He also scored twice – including the winner against West Ham in February. After joining us, Emerson made 41 appearances in all competitions in 2021/22, including 31 in the Premier League, starting our final seven matches as we secured fourth place and a return to the UEFA Champions League. Deployed as a right wing–back, Royal scored his first Spurs goal in our 3–1 win against Brighton in the FA Cup, and followed it up with his first league goal as we beat Newcastle 5–0 in April.</item>
        <item>Davinson made 12 starts in all competitions in 2022/23, eight in the Premier League, as he racked up 23 appearances in all competitions. That took him past the 200-appearance m The defender made his professional debut for Atletico Nacional aged 17 in his homeland of Colombia and was part of their Copa Libertadores winning side in 2016. He moved to Ajax in June, 2016, and made 47 appearances for the Dutch side, scoring seven goals. He won Ajax’s ‘Rinus Michels’ Player of the Year Award in his only season at the Club, which was previously won by Jan Vertonghen in 2012 and Rafael van der Vaart in 2002.Upon moving to Spurs, he made his debut as a late substitute against Burnley in our third game of the 2017/18 campaign, but quickly established himself as a regular starter throughout the remainder of a highly impressive first season in our colours.ilestone for the Club and hed moved on to 205 appearances in all competitions by the end of 2022/23.</item>
        <item>An Academy graduate who first stepped into a Spurs Development Centre at the age of five in 2005, Oliver Skipp is now an integral member of the squad. However, injury again played its part in Skippys campaign in 2022/23. Initially recovered from a nagging pubis injury that required surgery, the midfielder was then laid low by a foot problem that he picked up on our pre–season tour of Korea. That kept him out until early October, and it wasnt until Newcastle at home on 23 October that he made his first start since January. Nevertheless, Skippy grew back into the side and following injury to Rodrigo Bentancur in February, started 17 of our last 18 matches in all competitions, taking his tally to 31 appearances in 2022/23 and 82 in his Spurs career. Those stats now include his first Spurs goal, achieved in superb style, a belter in the 2–0 win against Chelsea in February, 2023.</item>
        <item>South Korean international superstar Heung-Min Son has endeared himself to the Spurs faithful with some fantastic goalscoring displays since signing from Bayer Leverkusen in August, 2015 - and in August of 2023 he was appointed Club captain. Now up to sixth in our all-time goalscoring list on 145 goals in 372 matches for us in all competitions, Sonny had another moment to savour in 2022/23 when he struck a beauty against Brighton in April - his 100th Premier League goal - the first Asian player to achieve that feat. Scorer of the first Premier League and Champions League goals at Tottenham Hotspur Stadium, winner of the 2019/20 FIFA Puskas Award for his wonder goal against Burnley in December, 2019, Sonny added the Premier Leagues Golden Boot to his long list of achievements with 23 goals in 2021/22, sharing the trophy with Liverpools Mo Salah.</item>
        <item>Initially deployed as a right-back, then into central midfield, Eric has now settled into a central defensive role and was a key figure as we finished fourth in the Premier League and secured a return to the UEFA Champions League in 2021/22. Eric continued his form at the start of 2022/23, so much so that he earned an England recall after two years in September, and then made it into Gareth Southgates squad for the World Cup in November/December. He appeared twice as England made the quarter-finals in Qatar, taking him up to 49 caps. Back in N17, his ninth season here, Eric made 42 appearances in all competitions, 40 starts, including another 33 for us in the Premier League. That took him up to 361 appearances in all competitions - taking him into our top 25 all-time appearance makers - and 270 in the Premier League, now fifth all-time in the competition.</item>
        <item>Influential midfielder Rodrigo Bentancur joined us from Juventus in January, 2022, signing a contract until 2026. After impressing so much after his arrival from Serie A alongside Dejan Kulusevski as we qualified for the Champions League by finishing fourth in 2021/22, Rodrigo moved up another gear in 2022/23 – until injury cruelly cut it short. Until February, 2023, Rodri had made 26 appearances in all competitions, starting 24, and contributed six goals. That included late winners in comebacks against Bournemouth and Leeds (where he scored the equaliser and winner in a 4–3 classic) in October and November. Rodri started all three games for Uruguay at the FIFA World Cup in Qatar in 2022 but was injured and had to leave the action early against Ghana in a dramatic finale to Group H, where South Koreas late winner against Portugal took them into second and the knockout phase by virtue of more goals scored.</item>
        <item>Experienced goalkeeper Fraser Forster joined the Club on 1 July, 2022, following the expiration of his contract at Southampton. A calm, commanding figure at the back, Fraser made 20 appearances for us in all competitions in 2022/23. He had to wait until November to make his debut in a League Cup tie at Forest, before making his first appearance in the Premier League against Brentford on Boxing Day. That ended a sequence of 101 consecutive starts for Hugo Lloris, and Fraser was called on another 18 times in the second half of the season, playing more than Club captain Hugo. Fraser had an initial run of nine matches in all competitions – including a return to Champions League football against Milan – after Hugo suffered a knee injury in the 1–0 win against City in February. Hugo returned in April, but Fraser was back between the sticks after Hugo sustained a hip injury against Newcastle that ultimately ended his season. Fraser went on to start our last six matches, taking his total to 20 in 2022/23, 14 in the Premier League.Experienced goalkeeper Fraser Forster joined the Club on 1 July, 2022, following the expiration of his contract at Southampton. A calm, commanding figure at the back, Fraser made 20 appearances for us in all competitions in 2022/23. He had to wait until November to make his debut in a League Cup tie at Forest, before making his first appearance in the Premier League against Brentford on Boxing Day. That ended a sequence of 101 consecutive starts for Hugo Lloris, and Fraser was called on another 18 times in the second half of the season, playing more than Club captain Hugo. Fraser had an initial run of nine matches in all competitions – including a return to Champions League football against Milan – after Hugo suffered a knee injury in the 1–0 win against City in February. Hugo returned in April, but Fraser was back between the sticks after Hugo sustained a hip injury against Newcastle that ultimately ended his season. Fraser went on to start our last six matches, taking his total to 20 in 2022/23, 14 in the Premier League.Experienced goalkeeper Fraser Forster joined the Club on 1 July, 2022, following the expiration of his contract at Southampton. A calm, commanding figure at the back, Fraser made 20 appearances for us in all competitions in 2022/23. He had to wait until November to make his debut in a League Cup tie at Forest, before making his first appearance in the Premier League against Brentford on Boxing Day. That ended a sequence of 101 consecutive starts for Hugo Lloris, and Fraser was called on another 18 times in the second half of the season, playing more than Club captain Hugo. Fraser had an initial run of nine matches in all competitions – including a return to Champions League football against Milan – after Hugo suffered a knee injury in the 1–0 win against City in February. Hugo returned in April, but Fraser was back between the sticks after Hugo sustained a hip injury against Newcastle that ultimately ended his season. Fraser went on to start our last six matches, taking his total to 20 in 2022/23, 14 in the Premier League.Experienced goalkeeper Fraser Forster joined the Club on 1 July, 2022, following the expiration of his contract at Southampton. A calm, commanding figure at the back, Fraser made 20 appearances for us in all competitions in 2022/23. He had to wait until November to make his debut in a League Cup tie at Forest, before making his first appearance in the Premier League against Brentford on Boxing Day. That ended a sequence of 101 consecutive starts for Hugo Lloris, and Fraser was called on another 18 times in the second half of the season, playing more than Club captain Hugo. Fraser had an initial run of nine matches in all competitions – including a return to Champions League football against Milan – after Hugo suffered a knee injury in the 1–0 win against City in February. Hugo returned in April, but Fraser was back between the sticks after Hugo sustained a hip injury against Newcastle that ultimately ended his season. Fraser went on to start our last six matches, taking his total to 20 in 2022/23, 14 in the Premier League.Experienced goalkeeper Fraser Forster joined the Club on 1 July, 2022, following the expiration of his contract at Southampton. A calm, commanding figure at the back, Fraser made 20 appearances for us in all competitions in 2022/23. He had to wait until November to make his debut in a League Cup tie at Forest, before making his first appearance in the Premier League against Brentford on Boxing Day. That ended a sequence of 101 consecutive starts for Hugo Lloris, and Fraser was called on another 18 times in the second half of the season, playing more than Club captain Hugo. Fraser had an initial run of nine matches in all competitions – including a return to Champions League football against Milan – after Hugo suffered a knee injury in the 1–0 win against City in February. Hugo returned in April, but Fraser was back between the sticks after Hugo sustained a hip injury against Newcastle that ultimately ended his season. Fraser went on to start our last six matches, taking his total to 20 in 2022/23, 14 in the Premier League.Experienced goalkeeper Fraser Forster joined the Club on 1 July, 2022, following the expiration of his contract at Southampton. A calm, commanding figure at the back, Fraser made 20 appearances for us in all competitions in 2022/23. He had to wait until November to make his debut in a League Cup tie at Forest, before making his first appearance in the Premier League against Brentford on Boxing Day. That ended a sequence of 101 consecutive starts for Hugo Lloris, and Fraser was called on another 18 times in the second half of the season, playing more than Club captain Hugo. Fraser had an initial run of nine matches in all competitions – including a return to Champions League football against Milan – after Hugo suffered a knee injury in the 1–0 win against City in February. Hugo returned in April, but Fraser was back between the sticks after Hugo sustained a hip injury against Newcastle that ultimately ended his season. Fraser went on to start our last six matches, taking his total to 20 in 2022/23, 14 in the Premier League.</item>
        <item>A quietly–spoken yet authoritative figure, Hugo Lloris is one of our longest–serving players. Following his arrival from Lyon in 2012, Hugo celebrated 10 years at the Club in August, 2022, having moved into our all–time top 10 appearance makers with his 416th in all competitions on the final day of 2021/22 – the day we clinched fourth place in the Premier League and UEFA Champions League qualification with a 5–0 win at Norwich City. The 2022/23 campaign was one of highs and lows for Hugo. In December, he led France to a second-successive World Cup Final, only to be denied history by becoming the first skipper to lift the World Cup trophy twice when Le Bleus were beaten by Argentina in a penalty shoot-out in a thrilling final in Qatar. He retired from international football after the tournament as France\'s most-capped player and captain with 145 caps.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_nationality">
        <item>Mali</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Argentina</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Colombia</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Korea Republic</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Uruguay</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>France</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/bissouma</item>
        <item>@drawable/maddison</item>
        <item>@drawable/porro</item>
        <item>@drawable/richarlison</item>
        <item>@drawable/romero</item>
        <item>@drawable/royal</item>
        <item>@drawable/sanchez</item>
        <item>@drawable/skipp</item>
        <item>@drawable/son</item>
        <item>@drawable/dier</item>
        <item>@drawable/bentacur</item>
        <item>@drawable/forster</item>
        <item>@drawable/lloris</item>

    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="data_wins">
        <item>20</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>63</item>
        <item>23</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>44</item>
        <item>23</item>
        <item>55</item>
        <item>124</item>
        <item>55</item>
        <item>34</item>
        <item>23</item>


    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="data_born">
        <item>August 30, 1996 </item>
        <item>November 23, 1996</item>
        <item>September 13, 1999 </item>
        <item>May 10, 1997</item>
        <item>April 27, 1998 </item>
        <item>Jan 14, 1999 </item>
        <item>June 12, 1996 </item>
        <item>September 16, 2000 </item>
        <item>July 8, 1992 </item>
        <item>January 15, 1994 </item>
        <item>June 25, 1997 </item>
        <item>March 17, 1988 </item>
        <item>December 26, 1986 </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_position">
        <item>MF(CM-DM)</item>
        <item>FW-MF(AM)</item>
        <item>DF-MF(DM, right) </item>
        <item>FW-MF(AM)</item>
        <item>DF(CB)</item>
        <item>Right-Back</item>
        <item>DF (CB) </item>
        <item>MF (DM) </item>
        <item>FW-MF(AM-WM, left) </item>
        <item>DF-MF(CB-DM)</item>
        <item>MF(CM-DM-WM) </item>
        <item>GK</item>
        <item>GK</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_appearances">
        <item>136</item>
        <item>164</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>201</item>
        <item>302</item>
        <item>46</item>
        <item>201</item>
        <item>234</item>
        <item>212</item>
        <item>223</item>
        <item>120</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>90</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="data_goals">
        <item>30</item>
        <item>23</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>31</item>
        <item>32</item>
        <item>44</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>1</item>
    </integer-array>


</resources>